In the dance of life, love can happen in a heartbeat.
Dance with Me is a drama, music, romance film directed by Randa Haines.
Young Cuban Rafael just buried his mother, and comes to
Houston to meet his father John for the first time.
The difficult part is that John doesn't know he is Rafael's father.
John runs a dance studio, and everyone prepares for the
World Open Dance championship in Las Vegas.
It soon becomes clear Rafael is a very good dancer, and Ruby is the
biggest hope for the studio at the championship.
Ruby Sinclair, played by Vanessa Williams.
Rafael Infante, played by Chayanne.
John Burnett, played by Kris Kristofferson.
Bea Johnson, played by Joan Plowright.
Patricia Black, played by Jane Krakowski.
Lovejoy, played by Beth Grant.
Dance with Me is a 1998 American romantic dance drama film
directed by Randa Haines and starring Vanessa L.
Williams and Puerto Rican singer Chayanne.
The film explores themes of dance, sports, dance
competition, musical, beautiful woman.
The tone is emotional.